Jhal
a very good evening friend it's losing ke varna
with aana online love you are on sure it's so Rakh
Vishwaveer welcome you to draw a question to a
drive from for mission possible
it's drawn mission possible that we can make the
mission possible to make everyday exam and the last
question is the question and on the roadside of the screen
you have parked your car are
you want to gate driver side and father from
behind and long long click on now you are the
and press the switch lights
bluetooth you have parked your car
come to the roadside you have to get out
what will you do at that time web so you have
these four options you will open the driver side immediately as
you pass you will
open your gate immediately or you will first check
that there is no one coming from behind
after that we will open our gate
here you will honk from a distance so that
people will know that you are there or
you will turn on your parking lights
so that people will know juice
sin  So now tell us to join
us quickly this is our last
question of the day and you can add to it
you can answer all of you you have
2 hours after that today's show will
end Andhra Jara Great Inner
Delhi's Ashok Gulati speaking up train
love so you can come join and
see your results whether your
friends have passed or not today also
request YouTube's Indica and your
family and friends and your loved one should I can be a
part of this campaign as well
and you can also in Hindi status for
girls of for road safety and make people aware it's very
important to be
connected for the same cords to make and everyday
for any how roller connect with everyday only be
used for going to off them back to home
go into market hospital and for research
in nuclear research switch on and
connected these officers withdraw
responsibility to make roads safer for
everyone so now like  I said that right now
our protest is our campaign connected to Dam
Anju Tom, if due to our foolishness and carelessness
some misses happen then it is
our responsibility to
stop them, we meet with accidents during processions
and we believe that we are not responsible,
after those accidents we are somehow
complicit in those things and how can you also be complicit,
if we do
not fulfill our responsibility, if
we do not follow the rules and regulations, then
we are complicit in that thing, so I
request you that whenever you go out
or if you are going by car, you should take two precautions,
you should follow your rules and regulations,
you should wear your helmet,
helmet makes covering, when you are
riding a two wheeler, some of the wheels are
very open,
they are
in direct contact, if some
pin is on that, then the chances of getting injured,
developing a transfer and getting damaged become
very high, so
whenever you ride a two wheeler it is very
important  Please wear helmets, it
forms a back covering over your hand and
it can protect you from a major injury. I mean
always buy the Sai Maa helmet,
yes I am wearing only the helmets
because it has a protective flame.
It is of very good quality.
They are mainly made to protect your heels. They go
through a lot of tests before reaching you, only then
they get the ISI mark stamp.
If you wear anything like that, then the helmet breaks automatically, so
how will it protect you? And propose to me,
please do
not forget to put a buckle or a crutch on your helmet so that it
remains tight to you and always buy a helmet of your required size.
Anyway, it is
very important for you to wear a helmet properly so that it should not be too
tight and if you have to drive properly, then it is
very important for you to
wear that helmet. Drive rough and try
whatever you can. And if you are an expert, I am
requesting you to kindly use
underpasses and foot overbridges.  Judges road to
congested and heavy traffic and always
smiling approach for this river crossing only
fever people can also think that there
is a cross sign here apk file name from
back but if you just run in the middle like this, there are a
lot of people who just
break these in between and
cross it, due to which there are
chances that they get caught
because the work that happens
in one season is done at peak speed
and during this time the drivers are not
able to apply brakes, then it is harmful for them as well as for
you and maybe it can happen to someone else also, so
please follow your rules and regulations,
this is the only purpose of this entire campaign
that we can make you and your day safe,
if we are able to change people then
somewhere we will make our day conditions
better, we say that
in foreign countries it happens like this, it happens like that,
if you see, if you try then
we can make our day also safe  If you are not
able to make it as good and as beautiful as Saif, then
you can see this work on my screen, like
you can see in the
screenshots last question of the day every day
for you for job car on road side
and getting out, you have parked your car on
road side, on you have to go out
that tube Upendra driver side, immediately
you will
open the driver side one, check for
cervical from behind and creep into it, you will
see from behind you there, and after that
now you will look behind, some artist Neera,
and after that you will open two, we will
Swadesh with blouse, know you are the palm, we will
switch on the
parking light, this look will be
known, so that
now their eyes can answer it,
all our avatars, in 2 hours, those
questions come, we
present the office located in Noida every day, start tax and go
till 7:00 pm, it runs in more happiness every 2
hours  In this game, questions come if there are explosives
and you can participate in five questions
and you can win
multiple prizes. We also request
you to help us in driving cars,
cooperate in making this mission successful. To
save your Taurus, to save your drives, to
save your life, to save the life of yourself and your
loved ones. By
becoming a part of this campaign and with us, we will
help you in making the country successful.
Somewhere or the other, it is very beneficial for you and your
loved ones. You
can see the question that is flashing on the screen, come
quickly.
On a daily basis, you have to go to get some stuff, so
many times it happens that
you park your car on the room side
and you have to wait a lot. Then
what will you do in that situation at that time,
you tell us and you have a chance to give the
correct answer, to enhance your skills,
your driving behavior, to
win exciting prizes.
Our entire question on daily basis
is about road safety to make people aware
and moving in this direction,
today we all need your support,
you can also be a part of this campaign by joining us, you
can make your day simple, it is
very important on guava because
if you do not go home then someone at home is
waiting for you that you will
come back, then you should go and keep that thing in
good condition and
always take care of yourself and your loved ones so that
we can make our day simple, come quickly
join us, there are 2 hours left unsafe,
after that all entries will be cancelled,
after that you will not be able to do 500,
in this lot only request you to come and join the
stamp in a is
and this skin cycle is printed this question in the
integration car on road side and you are
getting all Dual app has parked your car on the stop
side and you have to come out now
what will you do Vindhya driver will
open the driver side and immediately the driver side side will be on the
check it  Car from behind and open the door, look
behind to see if anyone else is coming
and then after that, now we will join from this point so that
people know that there is
parking, we will turn on the parking light there and
subscribe to this village.
So come and register yourself and
tell us about yourself and
tell us how much knowledge you have
about this. IES So everyone knows what
you should do when. The most important thing is to implement all the rules
and regulations. Understand this and you will start
implementing the
rules and regulations in your life. Like,
you have to stop your car before any crossing. You should
not cross the red line. You should
not overspeed. There is a
speed limit for every place, so
this is also the speed limit only.
You should not overspeed.
You should not drive at that limited speed
because friends are behind.
Best on
in a crowded area, how much problem is there in
that area, you should adjust the speed accordingly.
And ultimately, carelessness becomes the reason for someone else's common death. There will be well-
equipped raids
in reducing weight. The truth is that please take care of yourself and your loved ones. Whatever your
interests are related to, whatever
your things are, please take care of them.
Astrologer should tell you, add a blast. So many
answers are coming, so many tears are going
from your side. Hurry up and
enrich yourself. You have a
chance, um, gift,
enhance your good fortune. This question again, you hide park
your car on the road side and you are getting on which way
you will. You have parked your car on the
road side. You have to come out. Now what will we do,
immediately open the driver's side. Now it is with the driver.
Check it, why brother? Tomorrow from behind and
open the door. You will check the viewers from one side behind.
After that, open your net. Delhi State
President, not you, will be from the side. He should
know that it is here. We will turn on the switch on the light.
Okay, no, what will you do?
Subscribe and subscribe to this.
Thank you so much I love you all the
questions I just
amazed you possibly see you tomorrow with another
set of questions thank you so much oo hua
hai